COME ON
Come on!
owareru youni
Running like a fugitive,
isoi de iru
being chased by something.
kawai ta mune ga
Inside my heart is pounding,
kari tateru no sa
my throat dry like it's withering.
dare no tame de naku
For no single one,
dare no mono de naku
to none does belong,
ore tachi no ima ga
this time is ours, right now...
itami hodoki kokoro hodoki kage o hodoki
Unraveling the pain, unraveling our hearts, unraveling shadows.
iki o tsunete hashiri nukero yami o saite
Stifling our breath, reaching for beyond, tearing through the dark.
tatakau koto mo aishi au koto mo
In fighting and in love.
owari wa shinai
To the distant light above,
ON THE WAY
yes, we are on the way!
I WANNA ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
I wanna rock... Rockin' my heart...
Zabuza Disperses
Into the Snow...
Gato, why did you come here?
And who are those henchmen?
Our strategy has changed
a little...
I'm sorry about this Zabuza,
but you will die here.
What?!
Since hiring a regular Shinobi
costs a lot of money,
I hired Rogue Ninja like you.
And, it would have been even
more ideal
to save my money and effort if
Shinobi-to-Shinobi battles
ended in each killing the other off.
Well, you are certainly not worthy
of being called
the Demon of the
Hidden Mist Village.
If you were to ask me,
you're just a cute little demon!
What are those guys?
So many of them...
Kakashi... I apologize.
Our fight ends here...
As long as my reason to
take down Tazuna is gone,
there is no reason to fight you either.
Yeah... you are right.
That reminds me...
I owe him something.
He squeezed my arm 'til it broke...
Huh, he's dead.
You bastard!
What do you think you're doing, hey?!
Stop! Don't act so recklessly...!
You say something, too!
He was your comrade, right?
Shut up, punk.
Haku is already dead.
What...?
Don't you feel anything watching
him doing that!
Weren't you with Haku for a long time!
As Gato used me...
I was simply using Haku.
I thought I'd told you...
We Shinobi are merely tools.
What I wanted were his skills
and not Haku himself.
I have no regrets...
Do you...
Do you really mean that?
Naruto, stop.
There's no need to fight
him anymore... Besides...
Shut up!
My enemy is still... this one!
He...
He really liked you!
Is there someone special in your life?
He liked you that much!
When a person feels he wants
to protect a person special to him,
that person can truly become strong.
Even so,
don't you feel anything at all?!
It's difficult for me to completely
become a Shinobi.
You really... honestly...
don't feel anything at all?
I'd like to make that person's
dream come true...
For that, I could completely
become a Shinobi.
When a person becomes
as strong as you...
Does that person really
behave like you?
He threw his life away
for you!
I'd like to make that
person's dream come true...
That is my dream.
He didn't even fulfill his
own dreams and yet...
I was happy.
To die as a tool...!
That's...
That's... too painful...
Kid...
Don't say anything... anymore.
Haku was...
He wasn't just thinking of me.
He was feeling pain inside
for you
while he battled you guys too...
I know.
He was too kind...
I'm glad we could fight with you
at the end.
Huh?
Yes, little punk,
it's as you say, after all...
Shinobi are human too...
Maybe it's impossible to become
an emotionless tool...
I've lost.
Kid! Give me the Kunai knife!
Okay...
What?!
Enough! Take them down!
Right!
Are you crazy?
Do you think you can win by yourself
against this many of us?
D-Demon!
If you're so anxious
to join your friend...
you go ahead... alone!
Unfortunately...
I don't... intend on going...
to the same place... as Haku!
W-What?! Pretending to be so tough...
You're going to hell with me!
It's no big deal...
When the Demon of
the Hidden Mists Village
dies and goes to hell,
he can become a real demon.
Look forward to it!
I'll let you find out
for sure
if I'm a cute little demon or not in hell!
Haku...
Now... it's goodbye, Haku...
Thanks for everything...
I'm sorry...
Don't look away.
It's the end for
a man who lived fiercely.
Yup...
Did I... die...?
Sasuke-kun!
Sakura...
Am I... am I...?!
Sakura, you're heavy.
Huh?!
Sasuke-kun...
Sasuke-kun, Sasuke-kun, Sasuke-kun...!
Sakura...
That hurts...
Things turned out well,
didn't they, Sakura?
Stop, you shouldn't move...!
Anyway, where's Naruto?
And also,
what happened to that mask guy?
Naruto's fine.
And... the masked kid,
he died...
Died? Did Naruto get him?
Well... I'm not really sure,
but he protected Zabuza...
I had faith in you.
You are awesome, Sasuke-kun!
You avoided getting inflicted with
any mortal wounds!
From the beginning... he intended to...
Naruto!
Sakura-chan...
Sasuke-kun's all right!
He's alive!
Huh?
He was feeling pain inside
for you while he battled you guys too...
He was too kind...
I see... He...
So, Sasuke's all right too...
That's a relief...
Hey, hey, hey!
You guys are too relaxed!
Damn Ninja...!
Killing our source of money!
Now that it's come to this,
there's no choice but to attack
the whole town and
take everything valuable!
Shoot, this isn't good!
Hey, Kakashi-sensei!
Don't you have a Jutsu
to annihilate them all at once?
That's impossible!
I've used too much Chakra!
Here we go!
Enemies who come any closer
to the island...
With all the might of
all the island's people...
will not be allowed to live!
Yeah!
Inari!
Heroes always arrive
on the scene late!
Inari... You guys...
Okay, I'm gonna help out, too!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
I can do that even
with my scarce Chakra...
At least, it will bluff...
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Kakashi Version!
So... are you ready to fight?!
No, we're not!
We've done it!
Sounds like it's over.
Yeah...
Kakashi...
I need to ask you a favor.
What is it?
His...
I want to see his face...
All right.
Huh?
Snow...
Snow at this time
of the year...?
Haku...
Are you crying?
Thanks, Kakashi...
You were always at my side...
At the very least...
I can be at your side in the end.
If it's possible...
I'd like to go...
to the same place...
as you.
This guy...
He was born in a village
where it snowed a lot.
I see...
He was a boy as pure as snow...
You'd be able to go, Zabuza.
The two of you... together.
But you know, Kakashi-sensei...
Hmm?
I wonder if the way a Ninja
should be
is really as these
two were saying.
Shinobi should not seek
the reason for their own existence.
What's important is to
exist merely as tools.
That's the same in the Land of Leaves.
I wonder if that's what
it really means
to become a real Ninja.
I guess... I guess...!
I don't like that!
Do you think so, too?
Hmm...
Well... That's why all Ninja live
trying to figure that
out without realizing...
Like Zabuza... and that kid...
Okay!
Huh?
I've just decided!
I'm going to pursue my
own Ninja Way!
I'm gonna sprint straight
ahead and pursue
a way that I absolutely
won't regret!
Thanks to you the bridge
was safely completed,
but we will miss you very much.
Take care.
Thank you for everything.
Now, now!
We'll come back for
a visit again, Tazuna!
For sure...?
Huh?
Inari... you're gonna
miss us, aren't you?
It's all right to cry.
Go ahead and cry!
I won't cry!
It's all right if you cry,
Naruto nii-chan!
Oh, is that so?
See ya!
Oh....!
You are so stubborn.
That boy changed Inari's mind...
and Inari changed the minds
of the village people.
That boy created a bridge
linking us to hope,
a bridge called courage.
So a linking bridge...
Speaking of bridges,
we need to name
this bridge, don't we?
That's true.
In that case,
I have a perfect name
for this bridge.
Yeah, what is it?
The Naruto Great Bridge?
How's that?
That's a good name.
Okay! I'll get back soon
and have Iruka-sensei treat me
to ramen as
the mission completion celebration!
And! And! I'll tell Konohamaru
tales of my heroic exploits!
Then I...
Hey! Sasuke-kun, do you want to go
on a date
when we get back to the village?
No, I don't think so.
Just like that...?!
You know! You know!
I'll go with you!
Be quiet!
Shut up! Naruto!
What? Are you sure
that name's okay?
This name is to wish that
this bridge will never collapse...
And someday, it'll be the name
of a very famous bridge...
A name heard around the world.
That's truly what I hope.
Cultivate your hunger before you idealize.
Motivate your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain, never coming down.
Break into the contents, never falling down.
My knee is still shaking, like I was twelve.
Sneaking out of the classroom, by the back door.
A man railed at me twice though, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting for people like me.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry...
Hey, hey!
Our Team 7 always
has the easy missions lately.
Meanwhile, there are plenty of
powerful Shinobi
like Zabuza and Haku in other lands.
Aren't there more exciting missions
where I can be more active?
Where I can use my Ninja Way
and my soul like... you know?
Next time:
"Enter the New Chapter! It's the Chunin Exam."
This is my Ninja Way!